Instead of a few hundred Facebook comments, he received 2,000.
Most were critical of the 5G expansion.
Sick huh, Edwin?
Yes.
But I just wanted to ...
By New Year, Ygeman went out-
-And said that a Russian disinformation campaign was behind it.
Russian trolls.
"Some interests want to whip up a negative picture of 5G"-
-"and disseminate uncertainty between state and citizens."
Then it became quiet until April 5.
SVT has investigated users who have commented.
We can't find Russian bottoms.
The tracks lead to an apartment on Södermalm.
-In who remembers section seven ... -We must talk about what 5g is.
That's how opinion -forming works.
People go together-
-To influence politicians to make good decisions.
It is not just opinion -forming, it is democracy.
Cheers for democracy.
Sometimes drives and criticism is perceived as invented.
You do not experience them as real because it sounds too angry and strange.
But you can't dismiss them because you don't like what you hear.
Hello, listen.
Can you just check if I ...
A critical debate is central to democracy.
You are not foam if you do not agree with Anders Tegnell and Stefan Löfven.
It is not wrong to think something else.
The holders and authorities must have their eyes on whatever they think.
-As the doctor Li Wenliang, who was one of the earliest to alert about Corona.
Errors are constantly noticed.
At the Public Health Authority's press conference-
-Where Emmanuel Karlsten last to ask a question.
By asking the question-
-He had a great deal of inaccuracy that the Public Health Authority had missed.
First, I have to get a clarification.
Did you say that for every confirmed case of Covid-19 there is 1,000 more?
I don't get the mat together.
Surely there are 6,000 confirmed cases in Stockholm?
If you start from the material you have calculated-
-The for each confirmed case there is a dark figure of 999 more.